arrivenews.com 2006-07-18

# industrialleaders.tradepub.com Privacy Policy

**IndustrialLeaders.TradePub.com Privacy Policy**  
**A division of NetLine Corporation**  

NetLine Corporation is committed to protecting your privacy while on TradePub.com and our branded websites. Please read our policy to understand how your personal information will be used while on our sites and how we work to make your online experience with us secure. 

**Information Collection and Use**  
NetLine collects information in several ways and on different points on TradePub.com and branded websites. We act as an agent to collect data for some of our partners. When filling out subscription forms, visitors are required to fill out personal data (name, title, company, address, telephone, fax, email and various industry questions specific to the demographic interests). The data collected is then securely passed to our partner or their agent for fulfillment.

TradePub.com and its' branded sites collect opt-in email addresses which may be used for periodic email messages announcing additions to the TradePub.com site and/or promoting 3rd party entities. Users have a choice to opt in for none, one, or both types of periodic email messages. Users who opt in to receive TradePub.com announcements only will never have their email addresses sold, shared, or rented. Businesses may purchase the right to mail to those users who have opted to receive 3rd party promotional messages, however, those mailing will be done by TradePub.com and the users' email addresses will never be released to the 3rd party. In all cases, email list subscribers are given the opportunity to opt-out on each mailing. 

Where personal data is collected on our sites, NetLine attempts to provide a link to this policy.

**Cookies**  
From time to time, a cookie may be sent from a NetLine website to a user's hard drive. Cookies remember information about the user to be recalled at a later time. Cookies are commonly used to customize pages for you based on your browser type or other preferences or information you may have provided the website.

If a user chooses not to accept cookies they may still use our sites, however cookies enable us to track and target the interests or preferences of our users to enhance their experience while on our site.

Some of our business partners may also use cookies on our site (i.e. advertisers), however we have no access to or control over these cookies.

**Log Files**  
IP addresses are used to analyze trends, administer the website, track user movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

**Sharing**  
NetLine may compile and aggregate general demographic data to share with partners or advertisers, however none of this information is linked to any individual or identifiable person. 

**Links**  
There may be several publication qualification forms that are linked directly on our partner's site. Although we strongly encourage our partners to employ similar security measures, we cannot be responsible for the privacy practices of other sites. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by NetLine's TradePub.com website.

**Newsletter**  
NetLine's TradePub.com website offers a periodic newsletter to which visitors may opt to subscribe. To register for this newsletter we ask for contact information such as name and email address. This information will not be sold, shared or rented. 

**Choice / Opt-Out**  
Our users are given the opportunity to 'opt-out' of having their information used for purposes not directly related to our site at the point where we ask for the information. For example, our order form has an opt-out mechanism so users who subscribe through us, but don't want to receive any further communication from us, can choose to keep their email address off of our lists.

Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter or promotional materials from our partners may opt-out of receiving these communications by clicking on the unsubscribe link at the end of the newsletter and we will immediately remove your name from our list. 

Users of our site are always notified when their information is being collected by any outside parties. We do this so our users can make an informed choice as to whether they should proceed with services that require an outside party.

**Security**  
NetLine takes every precaution to protect user information. When users submit sensitive information via TradePub.com or branded websites the information is protected both online and offline.

When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (i.e. credit card number or social security number), that information is encrypted and is protected with SSL encryption software. While on a secure page the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked.

While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user information offline. All user information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (e.g. billing clerks or customer service representatives) are granted access to personally identifiable information, and then only through password protected screen savers. Furthermore, all employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. When new policies are added, our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy and what they can do to ensure our customers' information is protected. Finally, the servers on which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment, behind a locked cage.

While NetLine will work very hard to maintain secure sites, no data transmission on the Internet can be guaranteed.

**Notification of Policy Changes**  
NetLine Corporation is committed to safeguarding your privacy online. As this policy may change from time to time we encourage you to check back periodically.

We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected. However, if at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we may use their information in this different manner.

**Additional Questions**  
If you have any questions about the security at our website, please send an email to [privacy-advocate@TradePub.com](mailto:privacy-advocate@TradePub.com), or call us at 408-884-1200.
